Morgan Nebiosini

A **Product Designer** who's passionate about crafting visually appealing inclusive experiences.

Design Experiences

Product Designer

Stavvy, Jan 2022 - Present

Worked in a fast-paced agile environment, partnering closely with multi-disciplinary teams to produce a wide range of visual concepts and directions for the product. Followed a user experience design process to execute high-quality designs. Collaborated with the design and front-end engineering teams to help evolve our design systems.

Product Designer

Freelance, May - Dec 2021

Worked closely with stakeholders and developers to translate business and user needs into scalable designs. Lead UX/UI projects by conducting user research, mapping of personas and user journeys, wireframing of design solutions and creating high fidelity clickable prototypes for implementation.

Other Experiences

Makeup Artist

Freelance, 2018 - 2020

Responsible for applying makeup to aesthetically enhance performers, entertainers, and other individuals for special events such as weddings or dates.

SUBC Facilitator

Sephora, 2017 - 2020

Coordinated daily classes for clients to learn about makeup and skincare applications. Led team meetings to discuss ideas regarding class and coaching. Provided education training for coworkers. Delivered constructive feedback to peers for consistent development. Utilized proprietary company technology to elevate client experiences.

Miscellaneous

Mica

Grassroots Design Fest, March 2021

Worked on cross-functional design team to develop a responsive website for More Than A Shop, a Non-Profit located in Baltimore, MD.

Roller Derby - SIDR

Graphics Artist & Skater, 2014 - 2017

Worked with a team of volunteer graphic designers to develop flyers. Skated as a member of the home team.

MorganNebiosini.com Morgan.Nebiosini@gmail.com 631-875-2315 Newtonville, MA

Education

Design Lab

Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

UX Academy

I was accepted into a year-long UX intensive program, working in close collaboration with industry design leaders.

Projects included:

- Mobile app
- Responsive web design
- E-commerce design
- Streaming Service app design

Treehouse

Sep 2020

Introduction to HTML & CSS

Digital Literacy Track

School of Visual Arts

Bachelor of Fine Arts Candidate Illustration & Cartooning

Skills

Design

Basic HTML & CSS

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Task & User Flows

Visual Design

Design Thinking

UI Design

UX Design

Design Systems

Tools

Figma

Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop

Framer

UserTesting.com

Jira

Confluence

Whimsical

Slack